GEORGE E. EYO

- ◀ Balogun-udu close, Idado Estate, Lekki, Ajah, Lagos, 101245 (NG)
- eyogeorge23@gmail.com
- 08136285727

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Mechanical Engineer and Data Analyst with ten years work experience in Mechanical/Pneumatic Engineering

Hands-on, successful Software Engineer, Mobile App creator and Web Developer with over a decade of verifiable success leading teams in delivering appropriate technology solutions for desktop and mobile products.

EXPERIENCE

Deputy Manager, The Kabbalah Center Nigeria. Lekki, Lagos

Jul. 2019 - Present

- · Website management
- · overseeing content updates performance monitoring.
- · Company data analysis and Software Development
- · Event planning
- Analyze all aspects of corporate logistics to determine the most cost-effective or efficient means of transporting products or supplies.

Website Designer, PureTech Marketing Agency.

May. 2016 - Mar. 2019

- Create Desktop applications using Python and Kivy
- · Implemented data analysis solutions
- Develop application-specific software.

Desktop Developer & Back End Developer, True Web Inc. Online

Jan. 2016 - Nov. 2018

- · Develop web applications using Django and JavaScript
- · Designed and maintained MySQL databases
- Develop application-specific software.



Skills	
flutter	
HTML	
JavaScript	
Excel	
Analytic Reasoning	
Python	
KivyMD	
Tkinter	
phpMyAdmin	
Languages	
English	

Yoruba

Efik

 Advise customer about or perform maintenance of software system.

Engineer, Cybele Cosmetics Ltd. Lagos

Jul. 2006 - Mar. 2014

- · Crimping Machine Repairs and Servicing
- · Semi-automatic Filling Machine Repairs and Servicing
- · Shift Planning
- Study industrial processes to determine where and how application of equipment can be made.
- Recommend design modifications to eliminate machine or system malfunctions.

N.Y.S.C, Kevwe Constructions Ltd. Ugheli, Delta State

Sep. 2003 - Aug. 2004

• Construction, Repairs and Maintenance of cooling towers.

EDUCATION

Udemy, Online

Python for Data Science and Machine Learning, Nov. 2020

Alison, Online

A Comprehensive Guide To Personal protective Equipment, Sep. 2014

The Polytechnic Calabar, Calabar, Cross River State

Higher National Diploma (HND), Mechanical Engineering, 2003

The Polytechnic Calabar, Calabar, Cross River State

National Diploma(N. D), Mechanical Engineering, 1998